Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, and so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in wonder.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We'll live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary lives.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in wonderland.
Nami, how you feeling?
Are you completely recovered
from your illness already?
Sure am. I feel great.
Hey!
How about we go say
goodbye to the old doctor
lady and that Dalton guy from the village?
Don't be so thoughtless.
We need to leave Chopper alone with Dr.
E for a while.
He lived with her for six years.
We should let them say goodbye in peace.
I'm sure it's going to be
really sad for them both.
Dr.
E acts all tough in front of us, but deep
down, I think she really is a kind person.
So, we're just going to leave
without saying anything to her?
Yeah, that's right.
Once Chopper comes back,
we'll go straight down the
mountain and set sail to Alabasta.
Sounds good to you, right, Vivi?
Yes, now that we have a
doctor coming with us. Doctor?
Well, in that case, I'll go
ahead and get the ropeway ready.
Hey, Luffy! Give me a hand!
I didn't even know there was a ropeway!
So cool!
Well, look at that.
It seems as if we have a
couple of patients missing.
Yes, they all left.
Directly disobeying your orders.
Oh, I see.
What am I going to do with them?
Dr. Ayn!
I need to talk to you right now.
Chopper, where have you been all day?
Hurry up and get downstairs.
You can help the men
take the cannons outside.
Please listen, Doctorine.
I'm going to become a pirate.
I'm leaving with the others right now.
What did you say?
I'm going out to sea.
I'm coming on board with
them as the ship's doctor.
I'm going to travel everywhere.
Stop this foolishness, Chopper.
Now listen, you know
you're my only assistant.
I'm the one who taught you
everything you know about medicine.
Do you really feel no gratitude
at all for what I've done? No.
No, that isn't true.
I'm incredibly grateful to you, Doctorine.
And I'll always love this land.
It's where I met you
and Doctor, after all.
Hmm.
Then you can just stay here.
If you think you can
find another home as nice
as this one somewhere
in the outside world,
you're sadly mistaken.
Those pirates aren't good
for anything, Chopper.
You'll end up dead on some
vagabond sword in no time.
I can accept that.
Don't sound so sure of yourself.
A reindeer going out to sea, that's the
most ridiculous thing I've ever heard of.
Yeah, I am a reindeer,
but still, I'm a man.
You can talk tough for now, but
you're still my assistant, Chopper.
If you want to leave, you're going
to have to go through me first.
Do you understand?
Dr. Reed.
You're still afraid of your own shadow,
and you're telling me you're a man?
Oh, please, don't make me laugh.
But, Dr.
Eam, these pirates, don't you see?
Shut up!
Let's go!
They like me.
Quiet, you!
No, I'm not gonna let you leave me!
You're staying!
Get back here, Chopper!
You can't escape!
I wonder what all that noise is about.
Who knows?
Whatever's going on, we'd better
hurry and get all this stuff outside.
If we aren't careful, Dr.
Karoo will start using
us for target practice.
Don't exaggerate. Come back!
I won't let you get away from me, Chopper!
They're scared of us!
What's going on?
There's a lot of noise
coming from the castle.
How inconsiderate, making all that noise
when those two are trying to say goodbye.
That's just downright rude.
I'm sorry, Dr.
Eaton, but I want to go out and
see the world beyond this island.
Why could someone like you
do on a pirate ship, Chopper?
Are you going to try to live some
fantasy like that, old quack?
No, you're wrong.
It wasn't a fantasy.
Doctor's research was finally completed
before he died. Oh, finally. Here he comes.
What's going on?
He's being chased.
Hey, we got the ropeway ready to go.
Everyone, get on the sleigh.
We're going to head down the mountain.
Hurry!
Hey, look at that!
What the hell is that thing?
That's the witch's sleigh!
What was that thing?
It looked like Dr.
Correa's reindeer.
And those pirates were
riding in the sleigh.
What's going on up there anyway?
What happened to Wapol?
I hope Dalton's alright.
That was fun!
Hey, reindeer, can we do that again?
You idiot, we don't have time for that!
I thought I was gonna die!
Hey, where am I?
What's going on?
Oh, Sanji, you're awake! You okay?
You really think that was
the best way to say goodbye?
A pet I was taking care of is being looked
after by someone else now. That's all.
Besides, I don't like long goodbyes.
Come on!
We have work to do!
We have to prepare a fitting
send-off! That hurts.
I've finally done it! This is it!
This reaction!
I've been waiting 30 years for this.
Doctor, it wasn't a fantasy
like she said, right?
You finished your work.
You accomplished your dream.
Or was that all a lie, too?
I've done it, Chopper!
My research is a success!
Did you lie because you knew how sad I'd
be if you died without completing it?
Nothing is impossible for a
man who raises a pirate flag.
Please say it again, Doctor!
All right young man, are you ready?
Yes, listen to me Kureha this dust special
What are you doing just shut up and watch?
It's coming from the castle Is Waffle
setting off fireworks or something?
No, those are cannon blasts
What's happening up there?
Watch for cannonballs.
It's too dark to see what
they're doing up there?
Dr.
Corgi, all the cannons have
been fired Then light them up.
Look
Oh, cool.
Yeah.
Wow.
After 30 years, this dust
finally completes my research.
This is just absolutely amazing.
I still can't understand
what that idiot was thinking.
I will make cherry blossoms
bloom in this country.
Once my invention is perfected,
this country is as good as saved.
Get out of here, you crazy quack!
I thought lizard eyeballs would work!
This is no ordinary red dust, Pereja.
This dust is designed
to attach itself to the
white snowflakes as they
come down from the sky.
The white snow will then become a beautiful
shade of pink for everyone to see.
Doctor!
Doctor Eve!
I promise you, I'm not going to shoot you.
See?
My name is Hiriluk. Dr. Hiriluk.
Tony, Tony Chopper.
Cool name, huh?
Anyway, that's what I'm going to call you.
You're going to become a great doctor.
I'll make sure of it.
Even if I should disappear right
now, my dream will come true.
I've had a marvelous life.
Thank you so much, Chopper.
Now have a safe trip, my stupid son.
Moonlit night, cherry
blossoms are in the air.
How can we not party?
They're a handful.
I hate to tell you, but your new
friends are about as crazy as they come.
My friends? That's right.
These guys can really be a lot to handle,
but now that you're one of us, you're
going to have to get used to it.
Yes!
Come on!
Conney, what in the world were you
doing frozen in the river like that?
That bird, ten berries, says he
slipped and fell into the river.
He's a clumsy one.
Be quiet, Mr. Bushido.
Huh? Yeah?
He said that the guy named Zoro was
swimming in the river and disappeared.
He thought Zoro was in trouble,
so he jumped into the river to help
and ended up getting frozen in it.
So this is all your fault!
So you were really able to understand
everything Kari was saying?
Yes.
I'm still technically half-animal by
nature, so I can understand what they say.
You can talk to animals?
Oh, wow, Chopper.
Between your medical skills and talking to
animals, you've got some amazing talents.
Don't be silly!
You jerk-flattering me like that isn't
going to make me happy or anything!
He sure looks happy.
Hey, what did you mean about
Chopper's medical skills anyway?
Well, Chopper here is a doctor
and a first-rate one at that.
Dr.
Kureha taught him everything
there is to know about medicine.
Impossible.
Chopper, are you seriously a doctor?
How cool! No way!
Really, Luffy, if you didn't know that,
what did you think Chopper was
when you asked him to join us?
The talking, transforming
reindeer monster.
Backup food.
Wait, oh no!
I was in such a big hurry, I
left my medical bag behind.
It had all of my tools in it.
Your bag?
But isn't this it?
Huh?
That is my bag.
It was in the back of the sleigh.
What was that?
What do you mean?
Weren't you the one who packed the
sleigh and got it ready for the trip?
That's amazing.
Doctorine must have known
what you were planning to do
even before you had decided
to leave the island with us.
What a kind woman.
Hello, I got snot on the chopsticks!
Here, eat it!
Stop, eat it!
Those guys, can't they see you're
having a sentimental moment here?
I'm sorry, Chopper.
Chopper?
You too?
All right, Straw Hat crew, attention!
Listen, all of you!
Come on, Sanji!
Oh, no.
Hey, come on, you guys!
Oh, we're crazy.
I propose a toast to
our new friend, Chopper!
I wonder if they've made
it off the island yet.
You know,
that reindeer friend of yours is a
first-rate doctor with a first-rate heart.
I'm very glad to have known him.
Those cherry blossoms of hero looks
really did lead to something miraculous.
But who'd have thought the
miracle would be that clumsy
reindeer going out to sea
with a group of pirates?
That kid.
Acting like he's a grown
man all of a sudden.
I have a feeling I'll
make a fine ship's doctor.
So what are your plans now that Wapol
has gone from the island for good?
For a long time,
I worked as the captain of the guard
under Walpole's tyrannical rule.
That's something that I still
need to make amends for.
I was thinking about leaving this country.
Trusting the citizens
to make a better land
for themselves without
me here as a reminder.
I see.
Is that what you've decided to do?
No.
I realize that leaving here isn't
the way to make up for past mistakes.
This country is rid of
its corrupt monarchy.
Its citizens are preparing to build
a new country that's all their own.
And I think if I stayed here,
I could find a way to help them build it
into the country that it's meant to be.
Maybe that will help,
by washing away some of the guilt that
I've carried around with me for so long.
Well,
it seems to me that you
certainly do possess the
strength of heart to take
care of this country.
Strength of heart is needed
to look after a country.
And it can be difficult to come by,
but I once saw it from a girl who was
no more than ten years old at the time.
Ah, the world's summit again.
What a useless event this is.
I'm tired of coming to
this thing every year.
Absolutely right, sir.
I wonder how much longer Drum
Kingdom can continue like this.
The rift between the monarchy
and the citizens keeps growing.
Oh, look!
It's the King of Alabasta!
Cobra Nefertari.
A king who is known throughout the
world for his benevolence and wisdom.
The revolutionist dragon.
This man's beliefs are very dangerous.
As world leaders, we should be aware of
the threat he poses to our countries.
In as little as five or six years,
he will likely become a prominent
enemy opposed to our interests.
Well, I don't know about the
rest of your dumb countries,
But mine's governed too well for my citizens
to be led astray by some revolutionist.
Go ahead and capture them if
you want, but leave me out.
It's ridiculous.
Fool!
You are a selfish fool!
Why do you think we've all
gathered here at the World Summit?
Just act responsibly for once.
No one talks to me like that!
Well, that summit was as
unenjoyable as all the rest of them.
Huh? That girl.
She's that idiot Cobra's daughter.
Oh, no!
My hand must have slipped!
What are you doing?
Sorry!
Princess Vivian!
Oh, excuse me.
If I'm not mistaken, you're the
princess of Alabasta Kingdom.
Wow!
It must suck to have
such a pathetic father.
Dammit!
What do you think you're doing?
No, stop, Yigarum. I'm fine.
My apologies.
I didn't look where I was going, sir.
That is quite a child.
At a world summit like this where all of
the most powerful leaders are gathered,
tensions tend to run high.
The slightest argument
can trigger an Alto war.
Knowing that, she refused to make a scene.
She's so young to be so wise.
What an annoying little brat!
Let's go, Dalton!
Forgive us.
You made me so proud today, Princess V.
That princess had great strength of
heart indeed and that hasn't changed.
She's remained strong all these
years she would make anyone.
Dalton please the desire to care for
our country hasn't faded from within us!
Either allow us to do
something we want to help?
Build a new country.
Here you look.
This country will be reborn
as you always wished it to be.
Just like your son, Chopper. Dalton!
You need to hear this!
I just remembered something
important that I forgot to tell you!
What is it?
Take a look at this!
It's him!
That's the Straw Hat
Pirate who defeated Wapol.
We're sure of it.
You mean he has a 30 million
berry bounty on his head?
Are you certain? Goodness.
They're quite a band
of rogues, aren't they?
Where'd you find this?
Well, uh, I completely forgot
to report this to you, Dalton.
I'm very sorry.
I guess it all happened about a week ago.
A man who seemed to be a random traveler
showed up one day over in Robeltown.
Strangely, it was a day
without any snowfall.
We have no idea where
on the island he landed.
Anyway, he told us something.
The man said he was
hunting down Blackbeard,
the pirate, who recently
attacked our island with his men.
And then, once he realized that
Blackbeard had already left, he said...
In that case, I have one more question.
Has a pirate wearing a Straw Hat
come through this area recently?
We didn't know, so he showed us
the wanted poster and said...
Well, if the guy I
described does show up...
If he does?
Deliver this message.
I will wait for him in Alabasta
for ten days and no more.
Don't forget.
Hey!
Hold on a sec!
You didn't tell us your name!
Oh, yes.
I forgot about that.
The name's Ace, gentlemen.
If you tell the Straw Hat
Pirate, then he'll know who I am.
Hey, catch that guy!
He ate and didn't pay his
cab in the restaurant!
Just give him the message!
Thanks!
So he'll be waiting in
Alabasta for ten days.
Excuse me, Doctor, but
is there something wrong?
You look puzzled.
Tell me something, Dalton.
Have you ever heard of
the man Goldie, Roger?
Goldie?
Do you mean Gold Roger?
I guess.
Is that what he goes by now?
From the looks of this,
the guy Chopper left this island and headed
out to Sea Whiff is no ordinary pirate.
The spirit of D.
It still lives.
What do you know?
So what is Alabasta, then?
It's the country where
Vivi's father rules.
Yeah,
except there's this guy
named Crocodile who's
trying to take over the country right now.
And Crocodile's one of the
seven warlords of the sea.
Who are those guys?
They're pirates who are given
authority by the world government.
The government actually supports pirates?
Yeah, pretty weird, huh?
And the seven warlords
are incredibly powerful.
You see, they go around defeating
other pirates one by one.
And that's why the government
supports the warlords.
The idea is to have the pirates
get rid of all the other pirates.
I'm really looking forward to
meeting this Crocodile guy.
Crocodile is considered a hero back home.
He helps get rid of the
pirates who attack Alabasta.
However, his good deeds only
appear good on the surface.
He is an evil man. In truth,
he's manipulating the
citizens of Alabasta to bring
about his civil war so he
can take over the country.
No one has realized what
Crocodile's doing yet.
Not the people.
Not even my father. Right.
Well, this should be fun.
All we have to do is beat
up that crocodile guy.
Yes, but in order to do that, we have
to avert the Civil War in Alabasta?
and get Baroque works out of the picture.
Baroque works?
Oh, yeah.
You don't know anything
about them, either.
To be honest, I don't understand
what's going on with them myself.
They have a really complicated system
of agents, bosses, and partners.
The system is actually pretty simple.
First, at the very top of
the organization is the boss,
Crocodile.
He's known as Mr.
Zero.
There are a total of
12 agents in one animal
who receive orders from the boss directly.
For the most part, these 12 male
agents operate as part of a pair
with a female agent. Mr.
One is paired with Miss Doublefinger.
Mr.
Two doesn't actually have a
female partner. Mr.
Three is the candle man we ran
into in Little Garden, right?
That's right, And his partner is
the painter, Miss Golden Week.
Oh, yeah.
That little girl.
Mr.
Four is next in line.
He's paired up with Miss Merry Christmas.
I don't know much more than
that about those two, though.
Then there's that snot
guy. Mr. Five. Snot?
Yeah, his snot is explosive. Mr.
Five's entire body can
be used as a weapon.
His partner, Miss Valentine,
has the kilo-kilo fruit powers.
That's the woman who can change
her weight whenever she wants.
The agents with code names from Mr.
One through Mr.
Five are known as officer agents.
They each possess one of
the Devil Fruit powers,
and they are only sent on
the most important missions.
Agents Mr.
Six through Mr.
Thirteen have the job of fundraising.
They make money for the
organization by heading
up the employees at the
entrance to the Grand Line.
Hey, what about that weird monkey
and chicken pair I ran into?
That's Mr.
Thirteen and Miss Friday.
They're the agency's punishment squad.
They punish any agent who
fails to complete a mission.
And there are more.
Under the Officer Agents
are 200 men called Billions,
and there are another 1,800 men under the
Frontier Agents that
are known as Millions.
Together they make up the secret
crime syndicate Baroque Works.
Let's see, 200 plus
1,800 equals, um, uh...
There are 2,000 of them? 2,000!
All right, I think I understand.
When are we going to get to
Alabasta so I can beat up Crocodile?
Uh, I don't think you
get it at all, Loopy.
If Baroque Works' sole objective
is to take over Alabasta.
Alabasta then I can guess what
that must mean the rest of the
officer agents as Phoebe called
them and their subordinates are.
Probably on their way
to Alabasta as we speak.
Yeah
I see so in that case we just
go beat up that's enough Luffy.
Just let it go.
Okay
I'm sorry, Mr. Toot. Mr. Bonclay, sir.
Would you idiots quit playing around?
Damn it!
Are you completely clueless?
Do you even know who I am?
I am Bonclay, a Baroque
works officer agent.
I strike fear into the
heart of anyone who sees me.
Hey, you, navigator, tell
me something. Yes, sir.
Does that little pea-brain of yours
remember what the boss's exact orders were?
Yes, Mr. Two.
The orders were to kill Mr.
Three on his way along the direct route
between Little Garden and Alabasta.
Okay, then.
Maybe you're not entirely
useless, now are you?
Taking a direct route means that
you travel in a straight line,
doesn't it, Navigator?
That's why we went straight from Alabasta
to Little Garden, isn't that right?
But then something seems to have gone wrong
with the plan, now hasn't it, Navigator?
We reach Little Guard
without so much as seeing Mr.
Three while on our way here.
Not me, that seems to indicate
that you fools missed Mr.
Three's ship entirely.
No, sir, that can't be true.
Hmm, it sort of sounds like you're
questioning my intelligence.
Not at all, sir.
Be quiet, you.
All we have to do is kill
the pathetic Mr. Three.
It should be an easy mission and one
at which we have no excuse to fail.
We must complete the mission soon.
If we don't, then Mr.
One and his partner will be sent
out to make sure I end up dead.
Clear enough for you!
Now, if you don't want to answer to
me, then you'd better get to work.
Looking for that Mr. Three.
I want this ship going as
fast as it can, you imbeciles!
We're heading to Alabasta immediately!
Yes, sir, Mr. Two, Mr. Monclay, sir!
What's this?
Pirates are attacking
towns inside the kingdom?
Don't they know this country
is protected by crocodile?
Who can tell what they're thinking?
A country where riots are constantly
brewing may be considered an easy target.
You'll go.
Naturally.
I do have a public duty to uphold.
How very kind of you, sir.
Yes, I'm a kind man.
We warlords are charged with protecting
the public from pirate threats.
We are heroes to these people after all.
As you are with me.
I've grown stronger having you by my side.
We've started on an everlasting ride.
I'm invincible when your love is near.
When I'm with you I have no fear.
Let's see how far we can make this go.
The world is ours.
Future's pride I know.
I see it shine.
In the distance.
Glistening like water.
When the sun rises in the dawn?